Pre
and Post Hospitalization Expenses
Claim then first option select your
Hospitalization Expenses Claim then
second option select your
next
page select Insured Details then Mobile Number and
Email ID mention the proceed button click on the proceed button click on the
second page state city
hospital name date of admission date of admission date of admission cashless claim then last
page mention policy holder bank
details mention the fourth page
submit your document submit select the proceed button click on the upload
documents and upload the claim submit
register
mobile number key OTP mention the OTP mention the final page mention the
documents details and confirm the
final submit button select the
claim register and submit the claim submit after 7
to 10 working days  Claim status me
email ya message ruam lo me update wand
me submit claim status yal take care p lo kya
cheque ch kov me claim approve aya ka
me original documents ICICI
lder key courier ch ashya aly undi insurance
company ki documents receive aya ka within in
7 to 10 working days lo me inchin bank
account k amount transfer avatu i p manam
claim intimation ala ivalo ch um kvela me
hospitalization plan aate claim intimation
aya mod ka Home Page Claim Option
Select Three Option and
Second Option Raise a Request Select
Next Page Details Choose
Select Name Hospital Admit Patient Name
Select Second Page Hospital Name
Date of Admission Doctor Name Region for Admission
Details Mention details Submit details and mention details Submit details
Me ko clim
intimation number generate
avatu mike e video nachin late like ya share
cheyi marini videos kosam e channel ne
subscribe
ya